The SCOAN Sunday Service
Good Morning once again.
Your spirit is lifted up.
I can't hear you.
Yes, so if your faith is enhanced and you have found yourself there,
what are we expecting from you?
The Spirit will increase to the degree you stand in reverence of His Word.
Tell your neighbour.
Are you with me?
The Spirit of God will increase to the degree you stand in reverence, in honour of His Word.
I hope you honour His Word.
Ask your neighbour, "How much do you value the Word of God?"
I can't hear you.
How much do you value the Word of God?
That is it. When you say, "In Jesus' name",
the power that flows from His name will be in proportion to your love for His Word.
"In Jesus' name!"
People see it as a tradition - "Amen."
Even if you don't believe, you say, "Amen".
The power that will flow from His name - "In Jesus' name" -
will be in proportion to your love for His Word.
"In Jesus' name."
So you can know if you love Jesus and
you can know how much you love Jesus through "In Jesus' name".
So some people say, "I know".
"How much do you love Jesus?" - they say, "I don't know".
If you don't know how much you love Jesus - okay.
"We used to pray at home" or when I'm praying, "In Jesus' name", you say, "Amen".
The power that flows from His name will be in proportion to your love for His Word.
You can know how much you love Jesus. Tell your neighbour.
You can know how much you love Jesus.
Again.
You say, "How much do I love Jesus. I don't know what you are talking about".
Any moment from now, I will say, "Be delivered!".
What happens determines how much I love Jesus.
"Be healed!"
The power that flows from His name - "Be healed" - will be in proportion to my love for His Word.
If there is no love, He cannot come into the scene.
"In Jesus' name" - He cannot come out - "What are you saying? What do you want me to do?"
Without love - no. Because Himself is love.
Ask your neighbour, "How much do you love Jesus?"
You can know.
Tell your neighbour, "You can know".
I can't hear you.
You can know how much you love Jesus.
To love Jesus more and more is by attending to His Word and keeping His Word in your heart.
Because His word is your life and health to your flesh.
People keep saying, "How will I believe?"
There is no other way to believe than to act on what God has spoken.
That is it.
Act on what God has what? - Spoken.
Thou shall not kill, thou shall not destroy, though shall not this.
Act on what God has spoken.
Believing demands action.
Action.
The problem of believing is made easy, simple
when we know that it is acting on what God has spoken.
Simple.
"How will I believe now? I thought I believe."
That is why the book of Romans 10:9-10 says that in our heart we believe.
How can we believe in our heart?
To believe in our heart means our spirit - that is our heart - acting upon the Word.
That is the meaning.
Our heart - means spirit - acts upon the Word of God.
That means, it is not mental assent, it is not something we can memorise;
it must become an integral part of you.
When the Word of God begins to dominate your heart, you begin to believe.
Can you see?
It is not when you memorise.
When it is here, you can preach or teach it. - No.
When the Word of God begins to dominate your heart - that is your spirit - you begin to believe.
When you begin to believe, your character and your conduct will begin to be influenced.
The way you behaved before - you lie - you are just seeing yourself, "Thou shall not lie!"
You hate - you realise, "Thou shall not hate!"
Acting on the Word is letting God act through you.
Acting on the Word then gives God an opportunity to heal you, to talk to you,
to eat with you and to speak to you.
All what you are seeing talks much about faith.
Don't forget that it is this faith that releases the belief in our heart.
The belief will remain locked but faith will take the key, open and ask the belief to come out.
If not, the belief will remain there perpetually but faith unlocks the belief.
"Since I believe" but where is the faith to open the door for belief to come out?
Christians believe today but their belief is dormant because it is imprisoned.
Their belief is imprisoned without faith.
"I have money."
"Where is the money?"
"It is in the bank."
"Go and cash it."
But you cannot cash it.
You know that you have money. It is there. It is saved.
That is the same - belief without faith.
Faith is practical; it is action.
Like a good example I was giving you some time ago.
You pray because you saw the weather change, becoming darker,
and you are about to go to work.
It seems it's about to rain, and you need to go to work.
You now say that you are a Christian and go down on your knees
to say, "Lord, stop this rain!"
And you say to yourself, you have the conviction that God will stop the rain, and you say, "Amen!"
You laugh and dress up.
While going, you take an umbrella along with you.
What is the purpose of that umbrella?
In case it rains.
That nullifies your faith.
That is out of unbelief.
That is belief without faith.
It's like you were worried before that some people would come and disturb you - attack you.
Now you pray. After the prayer, you continue that worry, distress.
Belief without faith.
You are here for the salvation of your soul and some issue you want God to attend to.
Now having access to sit and watch, being right inside the church at last,
why do you still begin to worry again?
You believe without faith.
The belief in our heart is released by faith.
How can that your belief be released?
That's a good question.
The power that flows from His name, Jesus, will be in proportion to our love for His Word.
You can know if you are a Christian.
You can know how much He loves you.
You can know.
Can I ask you a question? How much do you love Jesus?
Very much.
Very much? Not how much Jesus loves you because He always loves you.
Okay?
How much do you love Jesus?
I believe that my life depends on Jesus. I can't live without Him.
You mean your life depends on Jesus; you cannot live without Him.
May you accept Him as your Creator?
Yes, I accept Jesus as my great Creator.
But you have not accepted Him as your Guardian.
He created you - you agree. But you would never agree that He should guide you.
That is it.
Are you with me?
You can create something and allow that thing to be guided by something else.
That is the life we live.
We accept Him as our Creator but we never see Him as our Guardian.
See Him as your Creator. Now see Him as your Guardian.
You can't create something and then give it to another creator to guide it - justl ike adoption.
You need to know how much you love Jesus, and not how much Jesus loves you.
Jesus loves you so much.
How much you love Him - that is the question now.
So how can you wake up in the morning, you pray without direction?
Not that you sense His presence to pray.
You just see it as a reason - conventional, the way you were brought up that you must wake up and pray.
At such time you must pray - not that you sense His presence,
not that He instructs you or you hear...
I mean, if I pray for you now - you say you are sick and I pray for you -
I must sense God's healing touching you before I can say, "You are healed".
If I do not sense God's healing touching you and I say, "You are healed", this means I'm fake.
I must sense God's healing touching you and say, "Ah, you are healed".
By the time you do this - "Ah, I am healed!"
I must sense God's healing touching you;
I must sense God's deliverance and God's blessing touching you.
If I don't know whom you are in the spirit, how will I be telling you -
"You are this, you are that", and just guess.
We don't follow Him in guessing, on our own.
Do you listen to what you are saying because all on your mind is to receive healing?
You don't know how much you love Jesus.
Yes, Man of God.
That is why you are here.
Yes.
Do you want to know how much?
Yes, Man of God.
By attending to His word, allowing His word in the midst of your heart
and seeing His word as your life and healing to your flesh.
Yes, Man of God.
You are here now for healing and you say you believe but you are still worried.
That worry nullifies your faith.
Okay, Man of God.
If you have faith - don't just believe but you have faith -
you'll begin to give thanks to God even when that healing has not even come.
Okay, Man of God.
Yes, Man of God.
Difficulty in walking due to lumbar spondylosis and osteoarthritis in my knees,
tighs, back, waist and feet.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Come.
Thank You, Jesus!
The reason why I said, "Come on" is because I could sense God's healing touching you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank You, Jesus!
Remove it.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
I am healed! Thank You, Jesus!
Thank you, Man of God!
Thank You, Jesus!
I can run! Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! I am healed!
For so many years suffering with arthritis!
Thank You, Jesus! I can dance!
The Spirit will be released to the degree that we stand in reverence of His Word.
How do we reverence His Word?
By attending to His Word and allowing His Word in the midst of our hearts,
seeing His Word as our life and healing to all our flesh.
What happened to this woman now has affected you there.
I mean, as this woman was healed, you were healed there. You don't know.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But he is still carrying the gadget - carrying everything.
"Until the man touches me or talks to me."
As the woman was healed here, I could sense God's healing touching you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Take this thing from your mouth.
Stand up, you are healed!
Healed In Jesus' Name
I can breathe!
I feel cold air coming into me. I was hot before but now I feel my body cold.
Why should I be the one to tell you?
Was it before I told you? Or?
As soon as that lady stood up there and started running, I felt the cold come to me.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Go and tell them! Tell people and mention that!
Look.
When ten sick people are together, if one is healed by the power of God, all the others are healed.
It is a flame; the power is like a smoke.
If I prepare fire here, the smoke that will come out, every assembly will smell it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If there is faith.